Kyle Condie

4794 South Dutch Hollow Lane, #105 Holladay, UT 84117 (801)599.9767 barber.von.frankenshtien@gmail.com

Skills

Most of my skills are in the service/customer service industry, however, I do have strong skills with technology as well. I have three years experience in various areas of retail including unpacking freight, stocking shelves, customer relation, running registers, working with a team, managing other employees, and opening and closing a store. I have over five years experience as a barber. Skills I've developed from that include an eye for precision and detail in artistic design, strong communication and conflict resolution skills, and good problem solving skills. I also have above average skill and knowledge with technology; primarily within the Android and Windows operating systems, and a fair amount with the hardware of computers.

Experience

December 2017 - March 2020

The Salt Lake Barber Company - Barber

- General business operations such as taking payments, managing cash, sharing information and answering questions for customers.
- Following strong sanitation and cleaning practices to ensure customer safety.
- Artistic design to achieve the customers desired results.

January 2015 - December 2017

Curriculum Barber Shop - Barber

- Following strong sanitation and cleaning practices to ensure customer safety.
- Artistic design to achieve the customers desired results.

October 2012 - April 2015

Hot Topic, Fashion Place - *Sales Associate, Key Holder*

- General retail work such as customer service, upselling, shipment and stock management, and working with a team.
- Advanced store operations such as opening and closing the store, opening and closing registers, counting and making deposits, managing others, and managing projects.

Education

- Highschool Graduate from Hunter High School in 2013.
- Graduate from Tim Hites Barber School in 2014.